[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the psychic that Henry consults in the movie Over Her Dead Body?", "correct_answer": "Ashley", "incorrect_answers": ["Agnes", "Rebecca", "Kate"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first actor to attain the rank of Brigadier General in the US Air Force?", "correct_answer": "James Stewart", "incorrect_answers": ["William Bendix", "Kirk Douglas", "Clark Gable"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At the monthly pancake breakfast, Ron explains the meaning of love to the news team by singing the 70s hit Afternoon Delight in the smash comedy hit Anchorman.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When was the Earths second highest mountain, K2, first climbed?", "correct_answer": "July 29, 1954", "incorrect_answers": ["July 29, 1934", "July 29, 1894", "July 29, 1944"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What protein is the main component of the hair fiber?", "correct_answer": "Keratin", "incorrect_answers": ["Fibrin", "Carnitine", "Chitin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Strange Case of Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde is a novella written by this person.", "correct_answer": "Robert Louis Stevenson", "incorrect_answers": ["Thomas Hardy", "Neil Gaiman", "John Fowles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Crimean peninsula has been under the control of multiple powers over the centuries. Although it is considered to be an autonomous republic, it is a part of this nation.", "correct_answer": "Ukraine", "incorrect_answers": ["Romania", "Bulgaria", "Russia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the original name of the famous Taylor - Burton diamond, sold for $1,050,000 at an auction.", "correct_answer": "The Cartier diamond", "incorrect_answers": ["The Excelsior Diamond", "The Regent Diamond", "The Sancy Diamond"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What portion of the Earth\u2019s surface do oceans cover?", "correct_answer": "More than two thirds", "incorrect_answers": ["One third", "Half of it", "One fourth"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The water bottle is the most popular type of drink container found in garbage cans.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What term is used the denote the terrestrial stage of the development of the young newt?", "correct_answer": "Eft", "incorrect_answers": ["Imago", "Elf", "Larva"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This novel centers around Florentino Arizas obsession with Fremina Daza who marries a wealthy doctor of medicine, named Juvenal Urbino.", "correct_answer": "Love in the Time of Cholera", "incorrect_answers": ["One Hundred Years of Solitude", "Like Water for Chocolate", "Of Love and Other Demons"]}]